Hinazuki's late?
She said she was going to give me my present today.
Maybe she's late because she
stayed up making something.
Satoru?
But...
Satoru!
Y-Yes?
What's wrong?
Worried about something?
Hinazuki!
Anybody home?
Don't tell me...
Rubber boot prints?
They're adult-male sized.
It last snowed two nights ago.
That means an adult male was here since then.
Hey, what are we gonna do?
Five musicians playing the flute and drums...
Today's a fun Doll Festival.
I took the next two days off from school.
Where's Mom? Out shopping?
Actually, a similar incident
happened the next city over.
The culprit was caught soon afterwards,
but now we have this.
We don't know who did this, but we'll have
to prevent it from happening again.
Well, yeah, but let me talk to the
school about the media blackout.
I'll call you right after I do.
Got it. I'll let the editors know.
I'm counting on you.
He must be one of Mom's former colleagues,
a TV Ishikari reporter.
We don't want kids
remembering an incident like this.
True.
So this is when it started?
I can understand being worried,
but it ain't your fault.
I couldn't do a thing.
Really?
I didn't want Hinazuki to be all alone anymore.
Well, you managed that.
It wasn't enough. I could've done more.
It's pointless to blame yourself
for something after it happens.
There's only so much one person can do.
Be it you or me.
Go back to school tomorrow.
You'll only get depressed being by yourself.
'Kay.
Now, let's eat before it gets cold.
There's something I need to tell all of you.
What I said about Kayo
staying home with a cold was a lie.
She's actually been taken to her
grandmother's place for family reasons.
It was all so sudden that she
couldn't say goodbye to you guys,
but I heard she's doing well in Sapporo.
Did she run away?
I heard her mother was beating her.
That's awful!
But this is good news.
Satoru.
Don't let it get you down.
Yeah. You'll see her again.
Satoru,
the Kayo story was something the school
and the PTA decided on together.
I ask that you go along with it for now.
Sure.
Sorry.
It looks like there's a media blackout,
but there's been a police car parked
near Hinazuki's place for the past few days.
Apparently, her mother's
also a suspect at this stage.
And only six days after Hinazuki's disappearance...
City Hall has issued an advisory.
You are to only leave the school grounds
accompanied by a guardian.
...the second victim disappeared.
It happened sooner than I expected.
Did you hear, Satoru?
About Nakanishi Aya from
Izumi Elementary School?
Yeah.
A friend who goes there told me she ran away
and is now at her grandfather's place.
That sounds just like Hinazuki.
The running away thing is a lie, right?
Is this a case of serial kidnapping?
While there were a few minor differences,
history was definitely
starting to repeat itself.
The investigation was made public,
but TV Ishikari only ran the story
during the early morning and late evening,
and city families with children were
advised to only tune in to TV Ishikari.
I'm home.
The police car that was parked
all day and night near Hinazuki's place
only showed up every now and then
after Nakanishi Aya's disappearance.
The focus of the investigation must
have shifted to "serial kidnappings."
Just ten days after her daughter disappeared...
Hinazuki's mother threw out a trash bag...
with a pair of half-knit gloves inside.
I'll give you your present tomorrow.
That's a promise.
Where am I?
Am I back in 2006?
23-1 on Fourth.
The victim is Fujinuma Sachiko, 52 years old.
We're currently searching for the prime suspect, 29-year-old Fujinuma Satoru.
We have an eyewitness testimony. Over.
Roger.
Are you Fujinuma Satoru-san?
Wrong.
You're wrong.
I didn't do it.
Damn it!
I couldn't save Hinazuki, my mother's
been murdered, and I'm the prime suspect!
That's the reality I'm facing right now.
I have to prepare myself...
and run away!
I could only think of hiding under a bridge.
I have no imagination.
It's not like it'd be on the news yet.
I need to think first.
Why was Mom murdered?
Is it because
she'd realized who the culprit was?
Was her cell phone in the apartment?
What about her bag?
They were both nowhere to be found.
Did the culprit take them?
Was it because there's a chance
she'd leaked information about him?
Shit!
My head feels heavy.
I wish I could get some proper sleep,
at least for tonight.
Well, eat up.
Thanks.
Sorry about today.
It's the first time you've gone AWOL.
Katagiri-kun was worried about you too.
Knowing you, I'm sure you had a good reason.
Anyway, eat first, talk later.
I will, thanks.
Oh, so you had a fight with your mother.
Yeah.
Old people can be pretty stubborn.
Feel free to stay as long as you want,
but be sure to make up with her.
Got it.
Want a beer too?
No thanks.
Damn, I'm out.
I'll go grab some more.
I was right to think he's an
annoying big brother type.
Sorry I lied to you.
After receiving a tip,
the police rushed to the scene
and found a woman's body, presumed to be
the mother of the apartment's resident.
The police are currently searching
for the missing male resident
as a person of interest in this case.
This seriously couldn't get any worse now!
Next up, sports.
Today, the Japanese soccer team left
for Germany for the World Cup finals.
How could I be so naïve?
No, I can't hold it against him!
He always tries to do the right thing!
Of course he'd give me up!
Son of a bitch!
Are you stupid?
Airi...
That's the first time you've
called me Airi, Satoru-san.
You know you can't leave your phone on.
They'll track you through GPS.
What are you doing? Hop on already.
You have to run, right?
Sorry you got dragged into this, Katagiri-kun.
I think you mean Airi.
And now we're even in terms of bike rides.
Are you sure you want me in your house?
You know what happened, right?
The police came to the restaurant today
and talked to the manager about it.
It was on the news too.
Then why?
Isn't it obvious?
There's no way you'd kill such a caring mother.
Oh...
Thank you.
No need to thank me!
I can't believe you're being chased when
you're the one who's hurt the most by this.
Trouble seems to follow you around, though, huh?
Like this one.
You left this at work the other day.
I took the liberty of reading
the part you had bookmarked.
It happened in your hometown
when you were a kid, right?
The Hinazuki Kayo-chan murder case.
I can't believe she died on
the day of the Doll Festival.
I cried when I read that.
Huh? Doll Festival?
Yeah. Says it happened on March 3rd.
Well, relax for a bit.
I have to go return the bike to work.
Don't take one step outside this room, okay?
The book's contents have changed.
So history can be changed...
If I can go back there one more time,
I can still save Hinazuki!
Oh, right. I slept in Airi's room.
To Satoru-san,
I think I should go about business
as usual today, so I'm off to work.
My family said they're going out at 10 a.m.,
and that they won't be back until after 8 p.m.
You can find the house
and bike keys next to the clock.
My mobile number is...
Not Katagiri?
I really don't know how
to thank you, Nishizono-sensei!
It's fine.
Your father has always helped me out.
Oh, no, let me!
My dad is overjoyed, too.
He's amazed how much one traffic light
and crosswalk has increased our foot traffic.
That just means your father is a smart businessman.
All I did was lend him a hand.
Besides, that's a school route.
We would discuss it often at city council meetings.
I'm heading home. Goodbye.
Sure. Bye, Airi-kun.
What's that?
Oh, takeout pizza.
You should've told me!
I can treat you once in a while.
Thank you, but that's okay.
It's for a friend.
O-Oh, a friend?
A-A girl?
Well, see you.
She's cute, isn't she?
I'm sorry! But she's only 17,
so she's kind of a child...
I should get going too.
Thank you!
Airi-kun!
Manager?
You forgot this.
It comes with
the current promotion, remember?
Oh, thank you.
Anyway, about Satoru-kun...
I can't imagine him killing his...
I mean, doing something like that.
I agree.
If you happen to run into him, help him out.
Sure!
I'll offer my support as well, so call me if you meet him.
Thank you!
Can I really close in on the killer by looking this up?
A kidnapping case in the city three years ago?
I do remember something like that happening.
The suspect was arrested three weeks later,
but he vehemently maintained his innocence.
What is this feeling?
Something feels off.
Why are you calling the police?
Airi-kun!
You told me to help Satoru-san out.
You said you would offer your support, too.
Y-You've got it all wrong, Airi-kun!
I was, uh, just worried about you!
Then why didn't you just say so from the start?!
I wanted to trust you!
I-I was worried about you...
That, I believe.
Sorry.
Please, I beg of you...
If you really are worried about me,
please don't call the police to the house
of the family that's taking care of me.
I'm sorry, Satoru-san.
You have nothing to apologize for.
If anything, I should thank you.
I managed to get some rest, thanks to you.
We can't go back to that house anymore.
Nah, it's for the best.
Speaking of which,
that's not your family home, is it?
No. My mother's brother and his wife live there.
My family home is out in the country.
Instead of finding a boarding house
so I could go to high school,
they told me to come stay
with them here in Chiba.
Can I ask you another question?
What is it?
How can you trust me?
It's not that I can trust you.
I want to trust you.
Back when I was in grade school,
I once went shopping with my dad.
The owner caught him trying
to leave with chocolate in his pocket.
We lived in a small town,
and the owner was a friend.
He said he'd forget about it if my father
admitted to stealing it and apologized.
But my dad adamantly refused.
That was the first time I heard
my calm and gentle father yell.
The owner was left no
choice but to call the police,
and my dad was suspended from his post
at the local farming co-op for three months.
I know because I was watching the
whole time!
I know you didn't do it, Dad!
My dad quit the co-op,
got a divorce, and left home.
I guess my mom thought he actually did it.
It's for my own sake that I want to trust you.
Similar to someone wanting to be trusted,
but the other way around.
Go back home.
Tell the police
I threatened you into hiding me.
Are you stupid?!
There's no way you can get away by yourself,
and I refuse to tell them that.
Could you stop asking me if I'm stupid?
Anyway...
I'll at least bring you a change of clothes.
The manager didn't call
the police after that, huh?
What is this?
What's going on?
Did Satoru-san find his mother's phone?
How?
No!
It's from the killer!
"Stay right where you are."?
A-Are you kidding me?!
No way...
No way!